thejibe.com 2019-11-24

# Privacy Policy | JIBE eCommerce

This Privacy Policy informs you what to expect in relation to personal information about you which is collected on thejibe.com and subdomains of thejibe.com ("our websites"), and how it is handled and processed.

For the purposes of the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) the data controller is The Jibe Multimedia, Inc ("The Jibe", "us", "we").

We take your privacy seriously. We acknowledge and agree that any personal data of yours that we handle will be processed with great care and in accordance with all applicable data protection laws in force.

By visiting our websites, and, at your discretion, submitting forms available, you accept and consent to the practices defined in this policy. If you are under 16 years of age you must obtain parental consent before providing us with any personal information.

## The information we collect

We collect personal data of our employees and potential employees, clients and prospective clients, suppliers, business contacts and website visitors.

This data may have been obtained either directly from you (for instance, by signing up for a newsletter or by requesting a quote) or indirectly from third parties such as public authorities, public websites and social media, affiliates, suppliers and vendors.

We may collect and process the following data:

  * Personally Identifiable Information (PII), including: name, age, gender, email address, home address, phone number, marital status, religion, income, and education.
  * Other non-PII data that you voluntarily provide by filling in forms on our website. This includes, but not limited to subscribing to newsletters, registering for an event, downloading a white paper or an ebook, or requesting a quote.
  * If you contact us, we will keep a record of that correspondence.
  * Any comments or content that you post to our websites.
  * Our websites collect personal data about your computer, including your IP address, operating system and browser type, for analytics and optimisation purposes. We also collect details of your visits, the pages you visited, resources you access or download, including traffic data, location data, logs and other communication data. Please see the Cookies Declaration for more information.

## How we use the information

The information we collect can be used to:

  * Manage our contractual relationship with you
  * Review and assess your job applications
  * Facilitate our communication with you.
  * Manage our business operations.
  * Comply with legal requirements.
  * Undertake data analytics and to improve your experience on our websites.
  * Fulfill your requests for white papers, ebooks, newsletters or similar content and other marketing purposes.
  * Meet your requests for information about our services
  * Notify you of changes to our services

## Sharing Data with 3rd parties

Information we collect and receive may be disclosed to third parties in and out of the European Economic Area to the following categories of recipients:

  * To our professional advisors, service providers and vendors in connection with a (potential) corporate or commercial transaction.
  * To any competent law enforcement body, regulatory and government agency, court or other third party where we believe disclosure is necessary (a) as a matter of applicable law, (b) to exercise, establish or defend our legal rights, or (c) to protect your vital interests or those of any other person.
  * To any other person with your consent to the disclosure.

## How we protect the information

We protect your personal information in the same way that we protect other confidential information that we have access to. We use reasonable physical and technical safeguards to help prevent access by any unauthorized parties.

We will retain personal information for so long as reasonably needed by us to provide our Services. We may also retain and use such information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

We use third-party vendors to provide our services. Such vendors provide to us hardware, networking, software and storage. The facilities of these vendors may be located outside of the European Economic Area, and your data will be subject to their data security policies.

We have put in place procedures to deal with any personal information breach and will notify you and any applicable regulator should a breach occur, when legally required to do so.

## Your rights

If your personal information is protected by EU data protection law, you have the following data protection rights which you may be able to exercise by contacting us using the contact information provided on our contact page:

  * The right to be informed - You have the right to be informed about the collection and use of your personal data
  * The right of access - You have the right to access their personal data.
  * The right to rectification - You have the right to have your inaccurate personal data rectified, or completed if it is incomplete.
  * The right to erasure - You have the right to have your personal data erased.
  * The right to restrict processing - You have the right to request the restriction or suppression of your personal data.
  * The right to data portability - You have the right to obtain and reuse your personal data for your own purposes across different services.
  * The right to object - You have the right to object to the processing of your personal data in certain circumstances.
  * Rights in relation to automated decision making and profiling - You have the right to restrict or object to automated decision-making processes or profiling based on your PII data.

## Changes to our Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to modify or amend this Privacy Policy at our own discretion from time to time. The changes will be published on our websites. Your continued use of our websites constitutes your acceptance of those changes.

This version was last updated on May 18, 2018.
